productivity growth
will accelerate
to the 4%
to 6% range
6% range
and be
sustained there.
Normally, we see
a cyclical peak
cyclical peak
around there and
around there
then it falls
back. We think
back. We
it will be
sustained, and
we think
that by the
end of this
end of
decade, real
GDP growth
could be averaging
more than 7%
than 7%
per year. Wow.
per year.
And I know
that sounds shocking-
sounds shocking-
Yeah given that
Yeah given
we've been at
3% for
125 years.
But it is
the history associated
history associated
with technology revolutions,
a step change
technology revolutions,
upIn GDP growth
The productivity increase,
GDP growth
the GDP growth
that you are
GDP growth
forecasting as
a result of
these disruptive
technologies, to what
extent is that
extent is
the result of
fewer people
doing more?
My question is
My question
about job losses
as a result
of this technology,
a result
because if everything
because if
that investors are
betting on when
betting on
it comes to
this AI revolution
comes true, it
AI revolution
means that companies
aren't going to
aren't going
need as many
people to do
people to
a lot more.
lot more.
What does that
What does
look like?